Brazilian developer with 10 years of experience as a graphic designer, so I'm looking for a company where both skills come into play.

I am proficient within React (HTML, CSS, JS) and I have a solid knowledge of Rest API using Node.js, Express, MySql (Knex.js).

With a background as a designer, I am also highly skilled in quickly mock-up ideas and I also have vast experience designing art exhibitions and catalogues.

CONTACTS

+45 42 59 45 75 tiago86g@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/tiago86g

behance.com/tiago86g



github.com/tiago86g

SKILLS





MySql

Knex.js





REST API

Postman





Firebase

Styled components





Storybook.js

UI/UX design





Typografy Branding

LANGUAGES

Portuguese

Native



Danish

English

Advanced



Spanish

Advanced





Tiago Gonçalves

EDUCATION

Hack Your Future - CPH Full-stack web development HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Databases, Node.is, Knex, React. 2019 - 2020

Superior School of Industrial Design / UERJ Bachelor of Graphic Design and Product Design Thesis: A typographic study for adult education 2006 - 2011

EXPERIENCE

Full stack developer HYF (anna.co)

Graphic designer

TUBA Denmark

2019 to 2020

Therapy and counseling for young people who have grown up in families with alcohol or drug abuse

- Chat app for internal communication in restaurants

- New visual identity, marketing campaigns

Graphic designer Fairytell IVS

2020

International app for children's books

Anna makes restaurant hiring easier.

- Design and adaptation of books to different languages

Nordic film festival created by the Danish Cultural Institute - Visual identity (logo, invitation, flyer, folder, catalog, poster,

Graphic designer Ponte Nórdica

(Nordic Bridge)

2016, 2018 and 2020

Exhibition designer

2019 to 2020

Camp

Exhibition space for art & debate about migration politics

- Development of a video streaming platform

- Designing and building the exhibition

- Graphic material for the exhibition

banner and social media)

Art Director Azougue Editorial

2011 to 2017

Brazilian publishing house focusing on artistic literature and cultural intervention

- E-commerce management VTEX platform
- Graphic design
- Contact point for authors, stakeholders and suppliers

Graphic design **RNP**

2009-2011

A platafrm that connects people and institutions in an environment that enables knowledge production.

- Creating design for complex data charts
- Design of presentation material for sponsors

TO PLANDAY

Frontend developer, driven to make things happen

I first knew Planday a few years ago just after moving to Denmark (I also had an experience with your competitor - Quinyx) and I nailed both because the biggest challenge about working in a restaurant is to deal with crazy schedules.

Nowadays from a developer perspective, it becomes even more interesting because I can see how important is to have all features working smoothly to provide the best experience. Working at Planday I am especially interested in build efficient frontend solutions. As your new frontend developer, I can deliver a high service quality with:

- Proficient Front-end development using modern JS, CSS and HTML (React.js with Styled components).
- Solid knowledge of RESTful API using Node.js, Express, MySql
- (Knes.js), Postman and Swagger.
- Optimize the cooperation between designers and developers.

A structured workflow

The way I work starts from small commits with predictable and easier to debug code, building reusable React components and resulting in an efficient and fast application. I also care a lot about the documentation to make it easily accessible to my colleagues.

With this behavior, I can keep an organized and structured workflow in a fast-paced environment. From that point, I can engage the team to give/receive feedback and make us improve the projects we are working on. Efficient collaboration and teamwork are key factors for me.

The link between designers and developers

I come from both worlds. With a background as a professional designer (10+ years experience), I am highly proficient in quickly mocking ideas with Sketch, Figma, and Adobe. My eyes are trained to look for structure and visual aesthetics in all that I do. Moreover, I will work as a link between designers and developers, being able to merge the two areas into an amazing solution.

Warmest regards,

Tiago Gonçalves

Call 42 59 45 75
Email tiago86g@gmail.com

Tiago Gonçalves

web developer and designer